Tell us about M.
>> Well, see M, she is um M. Yeah. Can I
show you some of my future plans? I
girl, I got you covered.
Let's leave.
She likes to be prepared.
I don't eat medicine.
Hey, ma'am.
>> Maybe a little too prepared.
>> Better to be safe than sorry.
>> Okay, thank you.
>> Well, it does pay to be prepared.
>> Hi, uncle.
Hi.
>> I'm so proud of her. I really can't wait
to see what's next for her.
>> Well, a good school, proper training,
and loads of support from me and Arwan.
And if you invest in her now, I'm sure
she can reach her full potential.
M was so excited to make that
presentation for her.
>> She'll do anything for Dalia's future.
She may be a little bit too much when it
comes to preparing and planning, but
it's because she loves us.
She loves us. She knows how protective I
can be about my family.
So, she's always ready to help and she
just gets me.
M is
she's really like family. Uh, sorry,
direct uh direct cuta. Wait lang.
Good idea. Good idea. Good idea.
[Music]